bootstrapstudio.io 2017-06-28

# Privacy Policy

## **Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy sets out how Zine EOOD uses and protects any information that you give Zine EOOD through its website, bootstrapstudio.io. 

ZineScripts is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. 

Zine EOOD may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from October 1st, 2015. 

### What we collect

We may collect the following information: 

  * Name; 
  * Email address; 
  * Other information relevant to your purchase of software from us. 

### What we do with the information we gather 

We require this information to deliver you a better service, to issue license keys and to prepare and deliver your software download. 

  * We may use the information to improve our products and services. 
  * We may periodically send promotional emails **** about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. 
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you by email for market research purposes or feedback. 

### Security 

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, **** we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

### How we use cookies 

Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual, and maintain your logged in state. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. 

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. 

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

### Links to other websites 

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

### Controlling your personal information 

If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by contacting us via our contact form on this website. 

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we are required by law to do so. 

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. 

Rev1. Oct 2015
